Here is a simple example that uses
这是一个简单的使用网格搜索来
grid search to find parameters for support vector classifier.
寻找支持向量分类器的参数的示例
All you need to do, is create a dictionary to define your parameter grid.
你需要做的是创建一个字典 定义你的参数网格
Using the keys for the names of the parameters,
字典的键是参数的名称
and the values for the list of values to check during grid search.
字典的值是网格搜索时你想要尝试的值的列表
Then, pass your model and parameter grid to the grid search object.
然后 将你的模型和参数网格传入网格搜索对象(grid search object)
Calling fit on the grid search object,
调用网格搜索对象的 fit 方法
we'll run cross-validation on all different combinations of
我们将对参数的所有组合进行交叉验证
these parameters to find the best combination of parameters for this model.
找到该模型最优的参数组合
Now consider if we had a data preprocessing step,
现在假设 如果我们已经有一个数据预处理步骤了
where we standardize the data using standard scaler.
其中我们对数据进行了标准缩放 (standard scalar) 以标准化
This may seem okay at first.
这一开始也许可行
But if you standardize your whole training set,
但是如果你将你的整个训练集标准化
and then use cross validation to evaluate your model,
然后使用交叉验证评估你的模型
you've got data leakage.
就会发生数据泄露 (data leakage)
Let me explain, grid search uses cross-validation to score your model.
我来解释一下 网格搜索使用交叉验证的方法来评估你的模型
Splitting your data into training and validation sets,
它将你的数据分成训练集和验证集
training your model on the training set and then scoring it on the validation set,
在训练集上训练 然后在验证集上评估你的模型
and it does this multiple times.
重复上述操作多次
However, each time this happens,
但是 每次这种情况发生时
the model already has knowledge of the validation set because
该模型会因为所有数据都根据整个训练集的分布进行了缩放
all the data was re-scaled based on the distribution of the whole training dataset.
所以已经保留了一些验证集的信息
Important factors like the mean and
一些重要参数 如平均数和标准差
standard deviation are influenced by all the training data,
受到所有训练集数据的影响
meaning the model may perform better than it really should on unseen data.
意味着该模型在未知数据集上可能比其原本的表现要更好
Since the information from the validation set
因为验证集的信息
is already baked in into the re-scaled values.
已经渗透到重缩放的数据里了
The way to fix this would be to make sure that you run standard scalar only on
修复的方法是确保你在交叉验证的每一折
the training set and not the validation set within each fold of cross-validation.
只对训练集而不是验证集进行标准缩放 (standard scalar) 操作
Pipelines allow you to do just this.
管道就可以实现这个目标
Now, since the re-scaling is included as part of the pipeline.
现在 因为重缩放包含在管道中
The standardization doesn't happen until we run grid search.
所以标准化只有我们在运行网格搜索的时候才会发生
Meaning in each fold of cross-validation,
意味着在交叉验证的每一折
re-scaling is only done on the data that the model
重缩放仅仅发生在用于训练模型的数据
is being trained on preventing leakage from the validation set.
防止了验证集的数据泄露
In addition, you can also grid search values within these data transformation steps.
还有 你还可以在这些数据转换步骤中使用网格搜索
As you can see, pipelines are very valuable to removing
因此 正如我们所说 在数据准备阶段
the risk of data leakage during the data preparation process.
管道技术在控制数据泄露的风险方面很有价值